Welcome back to my series where I
recreate Dairy Queen Blizzard flavors,
but lower in calories and higher in
protein. This is the S'mores Blizzard.
Let me show you how to make it. We're
starting off with a marshmallow base.
So, this is essentially my vanilla base,
but with some mini marshmallows thrown
in there at the end. You don't even have
to mix these in or anything. You can
just throw them in on top, and the
creamy will mix them in for you. After
freezing for at least 16 hours, all you
have to do is take the pine out, run it
under hot water for about a minute, and
then throw it in your machine on the
light ice cream set. You might need to
respin once or twice, but mine came out
perfect the first time. So then you can
just go in and grab your toppings. For
this recipe, I'm using half of a
Hornbullles chocolate bar. I know it's a
crazy name, but it's literally my
favorite protein snack in the game. And
then we're going to sprinkle on some
mini Lucky Charm style marshmallows,
graham cracker crumbs, and that
chocolate.